<?xml version="1.0" encoding="us-ascii"?>
<book>
  <config>
    <startPage>1</startPage>
    <title>Quilxotic Example Book</title>
    <author>Ben Sullivan</author>
    <email>quilxotic@sulli.ca</email>
    <website>http://www.sulli.ca/quilxotic</website>
    <usesHP>1</usesHP>
    <usesCash>1</usesCash>
    <usesHTML>1</usesHTML>
  </config>
  <page>
    <id>1</id>
    <image>header</image>
    <content><b>Welcome to Quilxotic</b>, the easiest way to create your own interactive fiction novels in the vein of <i>Choose Your Own Adventure</i> books, with the added inclusion of optional RPG elements like health and currency.
<br><br>
Creating your own novel is very easy. Simply create a new XML file in the Quilxotic folder of your device's primary storage. <i>Example.xml</i> is provided as an example. Do not modify this file as it is overwritten at each launch, instead duplicate it or create a new XML from scratch to make your own content!
<br><br>
NOTE: Quilxotic is in a BETA phase at this time. While basic features have been implemented I expect some users to encounter issues, especially as the content being created becomes more complex. Please do not give a low rating if you encounter issues, instead contact me at quilxotic@sulli.ca and attach your content.xml file so I can debug and push an update! Thanks for your consideration!
<br><br>
Quilxotic uses a simple XML-based page system. The content.xml file contains a series of pages, each of which have several attributes. Please see the documentation at http://www.sulli.ca/quilxotic for details on creating your own book!
<br><br>
If you run into any problems, visit http://www.sulli.ca/quilxotic for more information, or contact me at quilxotic@sulli.ca! I hope you enjoy this application!</content>
    <choice1>This is where your first choice will go!</choice1>
    <choice1Result>2</choice1Result>
    <choice2>This is where your optional second choice will go!</choice2>
    <choice2Result>2</choice2Result>
    <choice3>This is where your optional third choice will go!</choice3>
    <choice3Result>2</choice3Result>
    <hp>0</hp>
    <cash>0</cash>
    <deathMessage>This is the first page, so it's pretty unlikely the player will have died here.</deathMessage>
    <vo>voiceover</vo>
    <music>bgmusic</music>
  </page>
  <page>
    <id>2</id>
    <image>header</image>
    <content>...</content>
    <choice1>...</choice1>
    <choice1Result>2</choice1Result>
    <choice2>...</choice2>
    <choice2Result>2</choice2Result>
    <choice3>...</choice3>
    <choice3Result>2</choice3Result>
    <hp>0</hp>
    <cash>-99</cash>
    <deathMessage>...</deathMessage>
  </page>
</book>